droidgamers.com 2014-06-30

# DroidGamers

##  [ Privacy Policy](http://droidgamers.com/index.php/component/content/article/56-bottom-link-articles/bottom-info/189-privacy-policy)

Details
     Published on Tuesday, 23 March 2010 10:28 
     Written by ExtremeT 

Our privacy policy is pretty simple. All the information we collect on this website whether at time of registering or any other time for any other reason is kept private and is not shared, traded, transferred or sold to any 3rd party companies, websites, advertising agencies, email lists or any other entity. Your information is used for registration purposes only on this site unless otherwise notified by the administrator of this site which will only be in the event of contest winning, product shipping or any other method of relaying a product you've signed up for or purchased through this site.

If the information we need to send you your winning(s) from a contest or a product(s) you've purchased isn't available through your account, we will ask you for it at the time of winning/purchase. If it is available, we will notify you in some form to make sure the information in your account is correct so we can deliver whatever goods you are entitled to at that time.

We do not sell, trade, share or transfer any of your personal information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property or safety. Only general statics will be provided to outside parties such as advertisers in the form of things such as site traffic, male/female ratio to name a few examples but no personally identifiable information will be shared.

All of the information you submit is stored safely on our servers which are secure, monitored, backed-up and logged daily.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use the information we collect to personalize your experience on this website, to improve this website through your feedback and information we receive from you.

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

This privacy policy only applies to information collected on/through this site and not offline.

All third party links on this site have their own privacy policies and therefor we have no responsibility or liability for the content or activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

By using our site, you agree to our privacy policy.

This privacy policy can be changed at any time and changes will be posted and dated on this page.

For any questions regarding this policy, please feel free to contact us via email at 702records [at] gmail [dot] com
